Well, I'm gonna be doing
some brain stem histology...
...while you put yourseIf
on the business end of a sponge...
(Amy:)...and wash those beakers.
Wash those b... Oh, I get it.
Little hazing for the new fellow. Yeah.
Better keep an eye out for, what...
(Sheldon:)...shoe polish on the microscope...
(Sheldon:)...or mad cow disease
in my grilled cheese sandwich?
(Amy:)No, I just need those beakers washed.
Hippity-hop, quick like a bunny.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, you have
Dr. Sheldon Cooper in your lab.
(Sheldon:)You're gonna make him
do the dishes?
That's like asking the lncredible Hulk
to open a pickle jar.
(Amy:)Sheldon, you've never worked in a lab
Iike this before.
(Amy:)You have no experience
in the field of biology.
(Sheldon:)I have plenty of experience in biology.
(Sheldon:)I bought a Tamagotchi in 1998...
(Sheldon:)...and it's still alive. Let's do this.
(Leonard:)Where's Howard?
No, "Hi, Raj," no, "How are you, Raj?"